<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blair!</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on blair!</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 17:27:40 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blair-c.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rivals Academy</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/rivals-academy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blair-c.github.io/rivals-academy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Built with &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Hugo&lt;/a>, JavaScript + CSS, and &lt;a href="https://ffmpeg.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener">FFmpeg&lt;/a> + &lt;a href="https://imagemagick.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener">ImageMagick&lt;/a> for media optimization, with automated site builds via &lt;a href="https://github.com/features/actions" target="_blank" rel="noopener">GitHub Actions CI/CD&lt;/a> deployed onto &lt;a href="https://pages.cloudflare.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Cloudflare Pages&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Rivals Academy is the largest website surrounding the indie fighting game &lt;a href="https://rivalsofaether.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rivals of Aether&lt;/a>, serving as the central hub for those seeking resources to improve their gameplay. The site receives roughly 250k network requests each month, with a 100/100/100/100 &lt;a href="https://developer.chrome.com/docs/lighthouse" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google Lighthouse&lt;/a> score on most pages.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="lectures">Lectures&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The first main section of the site is the &lt;a href="https://rivals.academy/lectures" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Lectures&lt;/a>, a collection of strategy guide articles featuring 20+ authors, available in both English and Spanish.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SteamJoin</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/steamjoin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blair-c.github.io/steamjoin/</guid><description>&lt;p>Built with &lt;a href="https://go.dev" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Go&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://go-chi.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">go-chi&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://tailwindcss.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Tailwind CSS&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://discordpy.readthedocs.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">discord.py&lt;/a>, and &lt;a href="https://redis.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">redis&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>SteamJoin was originally created as a supplement to &lt;a href="https://blair-c.github.io/mentorbot" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Mentorbot&lt;/a> &lt;code>/invite&lt;/code> command, but now functions as a separate Discord bot and standalone service allowing users to quickly and seamlessly invite others to their Steam games.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-problem">The Problem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Over the years of the game&amp;rsquo;s lifespan, the &lt;a href="https://rivalsofaether.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rivals of Aether&lt;/a> gaming community&amp;rsquo;s preferred method to organize tournament matches evolved from using Steam search, to sharing your Steam Friend ID, to finally using Steam lobby links. This final process entails keeping a tab open of your own Steam profile, and copying the &lt;code>Join Game&lt;/code> button to send to each new opponent, who then copy/pastes this link back into their own browser.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Another Year of Spanish</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/another-year-of-spanish/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 17:27:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blair-c.github.io/another-year-of-spanish/</guid><description>&lt;p>Two years ago, after many failed past attempts, I began my most successful foray yet into learning a second language, roughly following &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jo4ds4mxuhU" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Refold&lt;/a> methodologies after having completed &lt;a href="https://www.languagetransfer.org/complete-spanish" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Language Transfer Complete Spanish&lt;/a>. You can read my one year update &lt;a href="https://blair-c.github.io/a-year-of-spanish" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the end of that update, I set myself the primary goal of reading and listening to 500 hours of Spanish content this year, and I&amp;rsquo;m proud to say that I did achieve this! 150 to 650 hours is quite a big jump, so let&amp;rsquo;s talk all about what this actually entailed, how I&amp;rsquo;m feeling about my progress, and how I plan to continue forward.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Year of Spanish</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/a-year-of-spanish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:31:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blair-c.github.io/a-year-of-spanish/</guid><description>&lt;p>At the start of 2023, a friend and myself both shared in our group chat that one of our resolutions for the year was learning Spanish. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely no stranger to trying and failing in this pursuit, having left high school Spanish and a few short-lived Duolingo attempts with not much more than &amp;ldquo;¿Donde está la biblioteca?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;La niña come arroz,&amp;rdquo; but by the end of the month we decided to team up as accountibility partners and give it one more shot.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Mentorbot 3.0</title><link>https://blair-c.github.io/mentorbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blair-c.github.io/mentorbot/</guid><description>&lt;p>Built with &lt;a href="https://discordpy.readthedocs.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">discord.py&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://redis.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener">redis&lt;/a>, Mentorbot is my longest running project by far, initially launched just a few months after I first began programming in 2018. As such, it&amp;rsquo;s been through a couple iterations alongside Discord&amp;rsquo;s API, and seen features come and go as the platform&amp;rsquo;s own feature set has expanded over the years.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Mentorbot&amp;rsquo;s original and most popular feature is seen above, serving as a quick reference for hitboxes or other game info with a link to the full data on the &lt;a href="https://blair-c.github.io/rivals-academy" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Rivals Academy Library&lt;/a>. You may notice here and in the next section that a number of my other projects have in a large way grown out of what were initially Mentorbot features, adapting the UX between Discord and traditional web.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>