<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>blair! on My New Hugo Site</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content in blair! on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rivals Academy</title><link>http://example.org/rivals-academy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/rivals-academy/</guid><description>Built with Hugo, JavaScript + CSS, and FFmpeg + ImageMagick for media optimization, with automated site builds via GitHub Actions CI/CD deployed onto Cloudflare Pages
Rivals Academy is the largest website surrounding the indie fighting game Rivals of Aether, serving as the central hub for those seeking resources to improve their gameplay. The site receives roughly 300k requests each month, with a 100/100/100/100 Google Lighthouse score on most pages.
Lectures The first main section of the site is the Lectures, a collection of strategy guide articles featuring 20+ authors, available in both English and Spanish.</description></item><item><title>A Year of Spanish</title><link>http://example.org/a-year-of-spanish/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 14:31:54 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/a-year-of-spanish/</guid><description>At the start of 2023, a friend and myself both shared in our group chat that one of our resolutions for the year was learning Spanish. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely no stranger to trying and failing in this pursuit, having left high school Spanish and a few short-lived Duolingo attempts with not much more than &amp;ldquo;¿Donde está la biblioteca?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;La niña come arroz,&amp;rdquo; but by the end of the month we decided to team up as accountibility partners and give it one more shot.</description></item><item><title>Mentorbot 3.0</title><link>http://example.org/mentorbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/mentorbot/</guid><description>Built with discord.py and redis, Mentorbot is my longest running project by far, initially launched just a few months after I first began programming in 2018. As such, it&amp;rsquo;s been through a couple iterations alongside Discord&amp;rsquo;s API, and seen features come and go as the platform&amp;rsquo;s own feature set has expanded over the years.
Mentorbot&amp;rsquo;s original and most popular feature is seen above, serving as a quick reference for hitboxes or other game info with a link to the full data on the Rivals Academy Library.</description></item><item><title>SteamJoin</title><link>http://example.org/steamjoin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/steamjoin/</guid><description>Built with Go, go-chi, and Tailwind CSS
SteamJoin was originally created as a supplement to Mentorbot&amp;rsquo;s /invite command, but also functions as a standalone service, allowing users to quickly and seamlessly invite others to their Steam games.
Core Functionality At its core, SteamJoin simply requests and parses Steam API responses, then uses the Steam browser protocol to redirect into Steam on success.
If a problem is faced, troubleshooting instructions are displayed instead.</description></item></channel></rss>